Don't sleep.
寝 て ないで
寝てないで
I'm happy.
嬉しいんだよ
Don't sleep.
寝てないで
close.
近い
Now, onto the pillow.
さあ、枕に
Put your hands under your legs.
手を足の下に回してさ
It's difficult.
難しいよ
i want to sleep.
寝たい
I want to see it.
見たい
Too full.
満たすぎて
yes.
そう
Open it.
開いて
Open here yourself.
自分でここを開いて
I haven't opened it.
開けてないよ
Have you seen it yourself?
自分で見たことある?
close.
近い
what happened?
どうしたの?
I'm not sleeping.
寝てないよ
It stretches a lot.
すごく伸びるよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Try sleeping nearby.
近 くで寝てみて
Please stretch your arms.
腕を伸ばしてください
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛 い?
I'm going to sleep.
寝そう
once again.
もう一度
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
TRUE?
本当?
Do you understand?
分かる?
big.
大きい
What are the differences in faces?
顔はどんな違いある?
Don't hide it.
隠しないで
Do you want me to touch you?
触ってほしいの?
Don't touch me.
触らないで
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
sour.
酸っぱい
Isn't this the second time you've seen breasts?
これさ、おっぱいの2回目にしない?
Can I go?
いけるかな?
like this?
こう?
difficult.
難しい
It feels good.
気持ちいいよね
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎ
once again.
もう一度
tired.
疲れた
Okay.
いいよ
Stab here.
ここにぺたーんと刺す
Hide your stomach.
お腹を隠して
I have a wish though.
願いがあるんだけどさ
Don't you look good?
顔よくない?
It's a roll piece.
ロールピースだよ
Don't say it's fine.
いいって言わないで
I want you to.
してほしい
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎる感じで
It's on.
ついてるよ
It's not on.
ついてないよ
I just want to live today.
今日だけ生でしたいんだよ
No.
ダメだよ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
I like it.
好きだよ
School is about to start and I have to work.
これから学校も始まって、 お仕事しなくちゃいけない
Do you care a little?
ちょっと大事にする?
Is it okay just for today?
今日だけでいい?
In front of four.
4つの前になって
Only the upper body.
上半身だけさ
The hand is
手は
enter my feet
俺 の足の中に入
It is.
れて
The next one won't be easy.
次 は楽ない
Here it is.
ここにさ
I fell on my stomach.
うつむせいに転んで
I'm glad I put it out.
やっぱり出しよかった
I promised.
約束したわ
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出た
It was really intense.
めっちゃ激しかった
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎてさ
Let's take a break.
ちょっと休憩しましょう